Okay so from here what we're going to do is sew this closed and you know as you can see the green is on the inside, the black is on the outside.
I don't want black thread showing on my green fabric because it's really pretty and I just want something that matches like this thread that I chose.
If you notice it's a really good color for that.
And the outside of course is going to be black.
So I have you know this funky little color for the green on top, the black is on bottom.
I'm going to go ahead and sew this closed.
You just line these up together.
I like to start right here on the button catch.
Sew that.
And we're just going to go right around the lip.
I like to back stitch on these straps also.
You can't never sew the straps too many times.
We're almost done here.
Okay, all we have left to do now is to sew two buttons on; one on the inside and one on the outside.